{
    "subject": "Maria_Adelaide_of_Austria",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Victor_Emmanuel_II_of_Italy",
    "human_readable": "Maria Adelaide of Austria is married to Victor Emmanuel II of Italy.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.979343831539154,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about the marriage between Maria Adelaide of Austria and Victor Emmanuel II of Italy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9589509963989258,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Maria Adelaide of Austria and Victor Emmanuel II of Italy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9444389939308167,
            "question": "To whom was Maria Adelaide of Austria married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9091914892196655,
            "question": "Who was the spouse of Maria Adelaide of Austria?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9019256830215454,
            "question": "Are there any famous descendants of Maria Adelaide of Austria and Victor Emmanuel II of Italy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8705068826675415,
            "question": "Was Maria Adelaide of Austria ever married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8275132775306702,
            "question": "Who is Victor Emmanuel II of Italy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7660492658615112,
            "question": "Is there a connection between Maria Adelaide of Austria and Italy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6185203194618225,
            "question": "What is Victor Emmanuel II of Italy's role?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.499562531709671,
            "question": "What are some historical events associated with Victor Emmanuel II of Italy?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Maria Adelaide of Austria is married to Victor Emmanuel II of Italy.",
            "html": "yago_30686_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Victor Emmanuel II of Italy's role?",
            "html": "yago_30686_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there a connection between Maria Adelaide of Austria and Italy?",
            "html": "yago_30686_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is Victor Emmanuel II of Italy?",
            "html": "yago_30686_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30686_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30686_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30686_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30686_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30686_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30686_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30686_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30686_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30686_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30686_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the requested format:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`\n\nThe documents provided contain multiple mentions of Maria Adelaide of Austria being married to Victor Emmanuel II of Italy, and her relationship with him as his wife. Therefore, the information supports the triple that Maria Adelaide of Austria is married to Victor Emmanuel II of Italy."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents provide multiple references indicating that Adelaide of Austria (Maria Adelaide of Habsburg Archduchess of Austria) was indeed married to Victor Emmanuel II of Sardinia, who would later become the King of Italy."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}